Guide to the Gamma Sigma Delta, Cornell Chapter records,1992-2000.
Gamma Sigma Delta, Cornell Chapter Records, 1992-2000
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Gamma Sigma Delta, Cornell Chapter records, 1992-2000.
37-6-3454
Gamma Sigma Delta.Cornell Chapter.
.6 cubic ft.
Includes handbooks, minutes, reports, newsletters, photographs, and banners.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Collection includes organization handbooks, minutes, reports, newsletters, photographs, and banners.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
Gamma Sigma Delta was an honor society of the faculty in the colleges of Human Ecology, Agriculture and Life Sciences, and Veterinary Medicine. The Cornell chapter recognized the academic achievements of students, faculty, and alumni of those colleges with nominations for membership and with special awards. The Cornell chapter no longer exists.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes handbooks, minutes, reports, newsletters, photographs, and banners.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Gamma Sigma Delta.; Cornell University--Societies, etc.; Cornell University--Students.; New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences--Socieities, etc.; New York State College of Human Ecology--Societies, etc.; New York State College of Veterinary Medicine--Societies, etc.
Form and Genre Terms:
Photographs.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Box 1
  - Gamma Sigma Delta Conclave, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Gamma Sigma Delta Conclave-Photographs of participants, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Gamma Sigma Delta Conclave, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Gamma Sigma Delta Conclave, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - History, Handbook, Constitution, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - History, Handbook, Constitution, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - History, Handbook, Constitution, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Treasurer's Reports, 1997-1999 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Press releases, correspondence, sample award certificate, 1996-1999 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - An Historical Account of the Cornell Chapter (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Initiation and Awards Ceremony, 1991-1999 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Annual report: Gamma Sigma Delta News Notes; committee meeting minutes, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - News Notes; committee meeting minutes, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Committee assignments and new officers, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Distinguished Achievement in Agriculture Award, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Grant - Human Ecology Partnership Program, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Annual report: Gamma Sigma Delta News Notes: committee meeting minutes, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - News flyers, 1995-1997 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Photographs - Awards Ceremony, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Photographs - Awards Ceremony, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Photographs - Awards Ceremony, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Photographs - Awards Ceremony, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Photographs - Awards Ceremony, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Photographs - Awards Ceremony, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Photographs - Awards Ceremony, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Photographs - Awards Ceremony, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Photographs and negatives, no dates (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Stationary (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Newsletters - National, 1996-2000 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Box 2
  - Two Banners (Box 2)
- Box 3
  - International Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 3)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1987-1996 (Box 3)
  - Exec. Committee Minutes, 1990-1996 (Box 3)
  - Secretaries Handbook, Cornell Chapter, 1998-1999 (Box 3)
  - Treasuer Reports, Nominations/Awards, Membership, 1989-2000 (Box 3)
  - Gamma Sigma Delta Membership, 1995-1999 (Box 3)